Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Records UA045
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Records
1970 -- 2001
1893 -- 2006
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences and Engineering
Dean of the School of Arts and Sciences
Office of the Dean of Engineering
UA045
30.1 Linear Feet 28 boxes
Arrangement
This collection is organized in seven series: Faculty information; Reports; Department files; Building and construction proposals and plans; Subject files; Correspondence; and Appointment books.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains faculty information, reports, departmental files, campus planning information, correspondence, subject files, and appointment books from the Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences, and Engineering.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences was created in 2001 from a division of the Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences and Engineering. The Dean of Arts and Sciences is responsible for all undergraduate and graduate departments and programs, as well as research centers and institutes under the scope of Arts and Sciences. The School of Arts and Sciences comprises the College of Liberal Arts, the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, as well as the College of Special Studies.
The Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences reports to the Office of the University Provost/Senior Vice President. The Dean of Arts and Sciences works closely with a Leadership Team comprised of Deans of Academic Affairs and Education at both the undergraduate and the graduate level.
Susan Ernst served as Dean of Liberal Arts and Jackson College for Natural and Social Sciences from 1997 to the split of the Office in 2001. In 2001 she was named the Dean of Arts and Sciences, a position she held until 2005. Kevin Dunn served as Assistant Dean of Academic Affairs within the Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences from 2002-2005.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty; Facilities; Administration and Governance
- Faculty Information, 1970 -- 2004; 1970 -- 2002; UA045.001; 4.8 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series is composed primarily of three types of records: Department Rosters, Faculty Rosters, and Faculty Information Sheets. The Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences, and Engineering kept the Department Rosters and Faculty Rosters in three-ring binders. Digital Collections and Archives (DCA) staff removed these records from the binders, and rehoused them in folders. The exact composition of the Department Rosters changed over time, but generally they provide a list of faculty by department along with tenure and salary information. The Department Rosters cover the date range of 1970 to 1998, with gaps for the 1993-94, 1994-95, and 1996-97 academic years, and are arranged chronologically. The exact composition of the Faculty Rosters also changed over time. Generally, they provide information on faculty tenure status, contracts, degrees held and leaves of absence. The Faculty Rosters cover the date range of 1970 to 1997 with no gaps, and are arranged chronologically.
  The Faculty Information Sheets are records completed by faculty members to report their class loads, research goals and progress, and current publications to the Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences, and Engineering for each academic year. These records primarily encompass the years 1994-1999. However, some documents are from 2002 to 2004--the Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences and Engineering split into two separate offices in 2001. Due to the close relationship of the records to each other and arrangement at the time they were received, DCA decided not to separate the records. DCA received these records in two separate groups (accessions). The first accession was received in 2004. DCA received the second accession in 2007 and the corresponding accession number is 2008.019. Please see individual folders listings for indication of which accession records belong to. Also, please see Collection Documentation in the DCA office for an item level listing of records received in accession 2008.019. Both accessions are arranged into one alphabetical run by Department.
  Arrangement
  Department and Faculty Rosters arranged chronologically; Faculty Information Sheets arranged alphabetically by department
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation.
  - Historical Data Binder, 1970 -- 1992; UA045.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Materials removed from original binder.
  - Tenure by Department Binder, 1970 -- 1993; UA045.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Full-Time and Part-Time Faculty and Deans Binder, 1978 -- 1989; UA045.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Lists Binder, 1991 -- 1992; UA045.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Department Rosters Binder [1 of 2], 1970 -- 1980; UA045.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Department Rosters Binder[2 of 2], 1980 -- 1986; UA045.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Department Rosters Binder [1 of 2], 1986 -- 1988; UA045.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Department Rosters Binder [2 of 2], 1988 -- 1990; UA045.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Department Rosters Binder, 1990 -- 1992; UA045.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Department Rosters Binder, 1992 -- 1993; UA045.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Department Rosters Binder, 1995 -- 1996; UA045.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Department Rosters Binder [1 of 2], 1997 -- 1998; UA045.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Department Rosters Binder [2 of 2], 1997 -- 1998; UA045.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Data Binder, 1970 -- 1988; UA045.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Data Binder, 1988 -- 1991; UA045.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Data Binder, 1991 -- 1992; UA045.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Data Binder, 1992 -- 1993; UA045.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Data Binder [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1994; UA045.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Data Binder [2 of 2], 1993 -- 1994; UA045.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Data Binder [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; UA045.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Data Binder [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; UA045.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Data Binder [1 of 2], 1995 -- 1996; UA045.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Data Binder [2 of 2], 1995 -- 1996; UA045.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Data Binder, 1996 -- 1997; UA045.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Art and Art History, Faculty Information Sheets, 1 of 2, 1996 -- 2001; UA045.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
    See Collection Documentation for item list
  - Art and Art History, Faculty Information Sheets, 2 of 2, 1996 -- 2001; UA045.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Biology, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
    From unknown accession
  - Biology, Faculty Information Sheets, 1 of 2, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Biology, Faculty Information Sheets, 2 of 2, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, Faculty Information Sheet, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
    From unknown accession.
  - BSOT [Boston School of Occupational Therapy], Faculty Information Sheets, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Chemistry, Faculty Information Sheets, 1999 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Child Development, Faculty Information Sheets, 1995 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Classics, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Classics, Faculty Information Sheets, 1996 -- 2001; UA045.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Community Health, Faculty Information Sheets, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Comparative Religion, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 2000; UA045.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Drama and Dance, Faculty Information Sheets, 1996 -- 1999; UA045.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
    From unknown accesion
  - Drama and Dance, Faculty Information Sheets, 2000 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Economics, Faculty Information Sheets, 1994 -- 1999; UA045.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Economics, Faculty Information Sheets, 1 of 2, 2000 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Economics, Faculty Information Sheets, 2 of 2, 2000 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Education, Faculty Information Sheets, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - English, Faculty Information Sheets, 1996 -- 1999; UA045.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
    From unknown accession; Includes American Studies faculty
  - English, Faculty Information Sheets, 1996 -- 1999; UA045.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - English, Faculty Information Sheets, 1996 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Geology, Faculty Information Sheets, 1995 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - German, Russian, and Asian Languages, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - German, Russian, and Asian Languages, Faculty Information Sheets, 1 of 2, 1996 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - German, Russian, and Asian Languages, Faculty Information Sheets, 2 of 2, 1996 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - History, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - History, Faculty Information Sheets, 1996 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Mathematics, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Mathematics, Faculty Information Sheets, 1 of 2, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Mathematics, Faculty Information Sheets, 2 of 2, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Music, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Music, Faculty Information Sheets, 1995 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Philosophy, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Philosophy, Faculty Information Sheets, 1995 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Physics, Faculty Information Sheets, 1 of 3, 1991 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Physics, Faculty Information Sheets, 2 of 3, 1991 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Physics, Faculty Information Sheets, 3 of 3, 1991 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Political Science, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Political Science, Faculty Information Sheets, 1 of 2, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Political Science, Faculty Information Sheets 2 of 2, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Psychology, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Psychology, Faculty Information Sheets, 1 of 2, 1995 -- 2002; UA045.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Psychology, Faculty Information Sheets, 2 of 2, 1995 -- 2002; UA045.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Romance Languages, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Romance Languages, Faculty Information Sheets, 1 of 2, 1989 -- 2002; UA045.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Romance Languages, Faculty Information Sheets, 2 of 2, 1989 -- 2002; UA045.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Sociology and Anthropology, Faculty Information Sheets, 1995 -- 1999; UA045.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Sociology and Anthropology, Faculty Information Sheets, 1995 -- 2002; UA045.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Urban and Environmental Policy, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Urban and Environmental Policy, Faculty Information Sheets, 1994 -- 2002; UA045.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Visual and Critical Studies and Museum School, Faculty Information Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Visual and Critical Studies and Musuem School, Faculty Information Sheets, 2000 -- 2002; UA045.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Info Form Summaries, 1991 -- 1993; UA045.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Info Form Summaries, 1995; UA045.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Information [General], 2001 -- 2004; UA045.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
- Reports, 1970 -- 2006; 1987 -- 2001; UA045.002; 7.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains general reports of the university received by the Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences and Engineering, Annual Reports of Departments and Committees submitted to the Office, and Strategic Planning Reports of Departments.
  This series is organized by accession. The bulk of the materials are arranged alphabetically within each box.
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Reports by Department, 1970 -- 1980; UA045.002.001
    Open for research.
    Accession number for these materials is unknown. Largely annual reports, Folders are arranged alphabetically and maintain their original labels.
    - Folder 3 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Civil Engineering, 1977 -- 1978; UA045.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
      20 years from date of creation.
    - Folder 4 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Civil Engineering, 1978 -- 1979; UA045.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
    - Folder 5 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Civil Engineering, 1979 -- 1980; UA045.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
    - Folder 5 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Classics, 1971 -- 1976; UA045.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
    - Folder 9 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Community Health, 1975 -- 1978; UA045.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
    - Folder 12 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Chemical Engineering, 1970 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
    - Folder 13 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Drama, 1971 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
    - Folder 21 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Drama-Summer Theater, 1977 -- 1978; UA045.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
    - Folder 1 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Economics, 1970 -- 1975; UA045.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
    - Folder 10 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Electrical Engineering, 1970 -- 1975; UA045.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
    - Folder 8 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Dean of Engineering, 1974 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
    - English, 1971 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
    - Folder 6 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Engineering Design, 1970 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
    - Folder 12 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Fine Arts, 1970 -- 1976; UA045.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Folder 16 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Geology, 1971 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
    - Folder 1 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): German/Russian, 1970 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
    - Folder 5 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): History, 1971 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
    - Folder 14 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Mechanical Engineering, 1970 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
    - Folder 13 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Music, 1971 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
    - Folder 9 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Mathematics, 1971 -- 1972; UA045.002.005.00020 (Box 5)
    - Folder 5 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Physical Education, 1971 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00021 (Box 5)
    - Folder 1 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Philosophy, 1970 -- 1978; UA045.002.005.00022 (Box 5)
    - Folder 1 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Physics, 1973 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00023 (Box 5)
    - Folder 5 Administration - Deans (A&S Budget): Political Science, 1972 -- 1977; UA045.002.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1983 -- 2005; UA045.002.002
    Note from Office of Origin: "These are offices who are no longer sending annual reports to Dean's Office"
    - Annual Report: Academic Resource Center, 1989 -- 1990; UA045.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Summaries [1 of 2], 1989 -- 1999; UA045.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Summaries [2 of 2], 1989 -- 1999; UA045.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Audio-Visual Lab, 1989 -- 1992; UA045.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Career Planning, 1989 -- 1991; UA045.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Center of Study of Decision Making, 1989 -- 1992; UA045.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Center for Environmental Management, 1990 -- 1992; UA045.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Center for Cognitive Studies, 1992 -- 1997; UA045.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Conference Bureau, 1992 -- 2000; UA045.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Committees, 2002 -- 2003; UA045.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Counseling Center, 2003 -- 2004; UA045.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Dean of Admissions, 1994 -- 1998; UA045.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Dean of the Colleges, 1997 -- 1999; UA045.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Dean of Language Arts and Humanities, 1997 -- 2000; UA045.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Dean of Students, 1993 -- 1998; UA045.002.006.00015 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: European Center, 1989 -- 2001; UA045.002.006.00016 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Executive VP, 1995 -- 1998; UA045.002.006.00017 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1993 -- 1997; UA045.002.006.00018 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Health Education Program, 1993 -- 1997; UA045.002.006.00019 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Health Nutrition Research Center on Aging, 1992; UA045.002.006.00020 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Health Professionals Program, 2005; UA045.002.006.00021 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Health Science, 1991 -- 1992; UA045.002.006.00022 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Health Services, 1990 -- 1992; UA045.002.006.00023 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Hillel Center, 1999; UA045.002.006.00024 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: International Office, 1983 -- 1995; UA045.002.006.00025 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Library (Arts & Sciences), 1993 -- 1996; UA045.002.006.00026 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Lincoln Filene Center, 1993 -- 1998; UA045.002.006.00027 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Natural and Social Sciences, 1996 -- 2000; UA045.002.006.00028 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Office of Professional and Continuing Studies, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.002.006.00029 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: President to Trustees, 1995 -- 1997; UA045.002.006.00030 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Programs Abroad, 1990 -- 1992; UA045.002.006.00031 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Provost, 1996 -- 1997; UA045.002.006.00032 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: From Provost to President, 1993 -- 1996; UA045.002.006.00033 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Research & Education, 1992 -- 1995; UA045.002.006.00034 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1992 -- 1997; UA045.002.006.00035 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: School of Dental Medicine, 1991 -- 1997; UA045.002.006.00036 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: School of Medicine, 1991 -- 1998; UA045.002.006.00037 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: School of Nutrition, 1993 -- 1997; UA045.002.006.00038 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: School of Veterninary Medicine, 1997; UA045.002.006.00039 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Student Activities, 1990 -- 1991; UA045.002.006.00040 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Summer School, 1993 -- 1997; UA045.002.006.00041 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: Tufts University Television (TUTV), 1997 -- 1998; UA045.002.006.00042 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report: VP for Arts, Sciences and Technology, 1996 -- 2001; UA045.002.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - Annual Reports by Department, 1988 -- 2002; UA045.002.003
    - African-American Center, 1989 -- 1990; UA045.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
    - African-American Program, 1988 -- 2000; UA045.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
    - Art and Art History, 1993 -- 2002; UA045.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
    - Asian-American Center, 1990 -- 1991; UA045.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
    - Biology, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
    - Chemistry, 1998 -- 2002; UA045.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
    - Child Development, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
    - Classics, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
    - Communications and Media Studies, 1990 -- 1996; UA045.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
    - Comparative Religion, 1990 -- 2000; UA045.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
    - Community Health, 1997 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
    - Day Care Center (Eliot Pearson Children's School), 1991 -- 1996; UA045.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
    - Annual Report: Dean of Admin, 1991 -- 1996; UA045.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
    - Drama and Dance, 1997 -- 1999; UA045.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
    - Economics, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
    - Education, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
    - Environmental Studies, 1994 -- 1997; UA045.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
    - EPIIC (Ed for Policy Inquiry & Int'l Citizenship), 1991 -- 1996; UA045.002.007.00018 (Box 7)
    - Experimental College, 1997 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00019 (Box 7)
    - Gallery: Aidekman Arts Ctr, 1992 -- 1994; UA045.002.007.00020 (Box 7)
    - Geology, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00021 (Box 7)
    - German, Russian, Asian Lang., 1997 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00022 (Box 7)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1992 -- 1996; UA045.002.007.00023 (Box 7)
    - History, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00024 (Box 7)
    - International Relations, 1997 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00025 (Box 7)
    - Mathematics, 1998 -- 2000; UA045.002.007.00026 (Box 7)
    - Music, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00027 (Box 7)
    - Occupational Therapy, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00028 (Box 7)
    - Peace & Justice Studies, 1995 -- 1997; UA045.002.007.00029 (Box 7)
    - Philosophy, 1997 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00030 (Box 7)
    - Physical Educ/Athletics, 1998 -- 2000; UA045.002.007.00031 (Box 7)
    - Physics & Astonomy, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00032 (Box 7)
    - Psychology, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00033 (Box 7)
    - Sociology & Anthropology, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00034 (Box 7)
    - UEP (Urban & Environmental Planning), 1997 -- 2001; UA045.002.007.00035 (Box 7)
    - Visual & Critical Studies, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.002.007.00036 (Box 7)
    - Women's Studies, 1990 -- 1997; UA045.002.007.00037 (Box 7)
    - World Civilizations, 1990 -- 2000; UA045.002.007.00038 (Box 7)
    - Wright Center, 1992 -- 1999; UA045.002.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - Reports and Strategic Plans, 1980 -- 1998; UA045.002.004
    Annual reports of departments, general reports of the university and strategic planning reports from Arts and Sciences departments; Accession unknown
    - Annual Report: American Studies Program, 1988 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - Annual Report: Biology Department, 1988 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - Annual Report: Center for the Study of Decision Making, 1988 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
    - Annual Reports: Committees and Departments, 1988 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
    - Annual Report: Community Health Program, 1988 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
    - Annual Reports: Departments, 1988 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00006 (Box 8)
    - Annual Report: Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1988 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00007 (Box 8)
    - Annual Report: Philosophy Department, 1988 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00008 (Box 8)
    - Annual Report: Sociology and Anthropology Department, 1988 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00009 (Box 8)
    - The Campaign for Tufts: Structure and Goals, 1980; UA045.002.008.00010 (Box 8)
    - Chemistry Department Reports, 1987 -- 1989; UA045.002.008.00011 (Box 8)
    - Ninth Report on The Signatory Companies to the Sullivan Principles, 1985; UA045.002.008.00012 (Box 8)
    - Tufts: The New Campaign, Development and Department Operating Plan Fiscal Year 1989, 1988; UA045.002.008.00013 (Box 8)
    - Tufts University in Context: A Comparision with Other Colleges and Universities, 1984; UA045.002.008.00014 (Box 8)
    - Tufts University Program Plan Summary 1981/82 to 1984/85, Institutional Planning Office, 1982; UA045.002.008.00015 (Box 8)
    - United States Department of Agriculture Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging, 1987; UA045.002.008.00016 (Box 8)
    - Strategic Plans: Arts and Sciences, 1981 -- 1998; UA045.002.008.00017 (Box 8)